paindoctor.com 2019-05-19

# Website Privacy Policy - Pain Doctor

Website Privacy Policy  2016-11-17T09:52:28-07:00 

_Effective October 1, 2015_

All of Pain Doctor, Inc. and its affiliates (PDI) comply with the Health Insurance and Portability and Accountability Act of 1996 (HIPAA). PDI’s [Notice of Privacy Practice](https://paindoctor.com/privacy-policy/notice-of-privacy-practice/) is located at [https://paindoctor.com](https://paindoctor.com/), [http://arizonapain.com](http://arizonapain.com/), and [http://coloradopain.co](http://coloradopain.co/). In the event that there is a conflict between this Website Privacy Policy and the PDI’s Notice of Privacy Practices, the Notice of Privacy Practices will control.

PDI understands that the privacy of your personal information is important to you. This Website Privacy Policy specifically applies to PDI’s websites, your activities and interactions with it. From time to time, PDI may change or update this Policy. Any updates will be posted and noted in a date change.

 ** _What information does PDI collect?_**

  * PDI collects information from you when you subscribe to PDI’s newsletter or fill out a form.
  * When ordering or registering on PDI’s websites, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name or email address. You may, however visit PDI’s site anonymously.

 ** _What does PDI use your information for?_**

Any of the information PDI collects from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience ( your information helps PDI to better respond to your individual needs)
  * To improve PDI’s website ( we continually strive to improve PDI’s website offerings based on the information and feedback PDI receives from you)
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site features
  * To send periodic emails

The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information.

At any time you can unsubscribe from receiving future emails. There is detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

 ** _Do we use cookies?_**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

PDI uses cookies to keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that PDI can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. PDI may contact with third-party service providers to assist PDI in better understanding PDI’s site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on PDI’s behalf except to help us conduct and improve PDI’s business.

 ** _Third party links_**

Occasionally, at PDI’s discretion, PDI may include or offer third party products or service on PDI’s website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. PDI therefore has no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, PDI seeks to protect the integrity of PDI’s site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

 ** _Online Website Privacy Policy Only_**

This online Web Site Privacy Policy applies only to information collected through PDI’s website and not to information collected offline.

 ** _Your Consent_**

By using PDI’s site, you consent to PDI’s Web Site Privacy Policy
